<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Resumes on Personal Blog</title>
    <link>http://jurgen-kluft.github.io/resumes/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Resumes on Personal Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-EN</language>
    <managingEditor>jurgen.kluft@gmail.com (Jurgen)</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>jurgen.kluft@gmail.com (Jurgen)</webMaster>
    <copyright>(c) 2016 Jurgen</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 06 Jan 2016 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://jurgen-kluft.github.io/resumes/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://jurgen-kluft.github.io/resumes/resume-en/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Jan 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>jurgen.kluft@gmail.com (Jurgen)</author>
      <guid>http://jurgen-kluft.github.io/resumes/resume-en/</guid>
      <description>

&lt;h2 id=&#34;technical-director-software-engineering:8ecf1b6ee153f5f9713e1277d3ae6be8&#34;&gt;TECHNICAL DIRECTOR, SOFTWARE ENGINEERING&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Results-driven engineer offering 20 years extensive experience within both professional and startup environments.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Able to transform project needs into cost-effective, secure and efficient approaches known for scalability, ROI and durability.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Innovator of smart solutions, systems and applications fueling improvements to the infrastructure and product.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proven leader and technical manager with more than 10 years’ experience; driving system architecture decisions and leading projects from initial phase through the release process.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Passionate and hands-on in many aspects of software engineering, from architecture, implementation and refactoring to code-reviews, profiling/optimizing and debugging.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Solid experience and knowledge on how to train and mentor junior, senior and lead programmers in programming methodologies and best practices to improve efficiency and quality.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;10 years’ experience in China working with and leading technical teams incorporating team members from China and other various countries.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A decade of working as a western in a Chinese culture with a solid understanding how to work within such a culture to unlock potential, efficiency and quality.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;personal-info:8ecf1b6ee153f5f9713e1277d3ae6be8&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;PERSONAL INFO&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Gender: Male&lt;br /&gt;
Date of Birth: June 19, 1971&lt;br /&gt;
Nationality: Dutch&lt;br /&gt;
Residence:  Shanghai, China (China Permanent Residence Card holder)&lt;br /&gt;
Address: 3-1506, 34 South Yili Road, Shanghai, China&lt;br /&gt;
Mobile: 18616793279&lt;br /&gt;
Email: &lt;a href=&#34;mailto:jurgen.kluft@gmail.com&#34;&gt;email me&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;technology-summary:8ecf1b6ee153f5f9713e1277d3ae6be8&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;TECHNOLOGY SUMMARY&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Languages/Programming&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;C/C++, C# (.NET 2.0 to 4.6)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Golang&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;LUA&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Assembler for  MC680x0, DSP560x0, Zilog and PIC micro controllers&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Python.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Systems&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Windows XP/NT v4.0/7/8&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;PSP/PS2/PS3/PS4&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Xbox-360/Xbox-One&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Nintendo DS/WII&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Cryptography&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;SHA-1, SHA-3 (Keccak)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Skein&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Merkle-Tree&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Block-Chain&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Network&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;TCP/IP, UDP&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Protocols; packet/messaging custom protocols, pub-sub, req-rep&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;P2P; DHT (Chord, Kademlia, Symphony), BitTorrent protocol, ZeroMQ.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Databases&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Redis&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;MongoDB&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;professional-experience:8ecf1b6ee153f5f9713e1277d3ae6be8&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;shanghai-virtuos-software-co-ltd-shanghai-china-http-www-virtuosgames-com:8ecf1b6ee153f5f9713e1277d3ae6be8&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://www.virtuosgames.com/&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Shanghai Virtuos Software Co., Ltd. – Shanghai China&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&#34;technical-director-software-https-en-wikipedia-org-wiki-technical-director-2005-to-present:8ecf1b6ee153f5f9713e1277d3ae6be8&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Technical_director&#34;&gt;Technical Director (Software)&lt;/a&gt;, 2005 to Present&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Develop, maintain and support tools and systems for the infrastructure of projects, console and mobile platforms using C/C++, C# and related tools. Analyze code for system testing and debugging; create tests to find, isolate and rectify issues; create and use tools to find performance and memory isues and create solutions to optimize and reduce memory usage. Managing a team of 8 to 30 engineers.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Accomplishments:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Reengineered multiple systems that fueled improvements to productivity, efficiency, responsiveness and maintainability. Developed code, system design and tests for many solutions, used tools and scripts to rollout updates.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Led, architected and participated in the design, testing and deployment of a data building workflow, cross-platform tools, memory and profiling components.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Developed modular, portable, thread-safe and ultra-high performance foundation and application infrastructure libraries.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Trained and mentored junior, seniors and lead programmers in programming methodologies and best practices.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Delivered an automation and data conversion tool set, enabling the company to be more efficient in handling this specific aspect from project to project.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Developed a &amp;lsquo;large binary data&amp;rsquo; management system enhancing &lt;a href=&#34;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Mercurial&#34;&gt;Mercurial&lt;/a&gt;-&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.mercurial-scm.org/&#34;&gt;Hg&lt;/a&gt; (a distributed version control system) that increased efficiency, availability and scalability tenfold.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Made it a standard for every project to have a Continues Integration process to validate code and data changes. This later was advanced with automated testing, reporting and publishing of application builds.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Introduced and helped integrating &lt;a href=&#34;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Scrum_(software_development&#34;&gt;SCRUM&lt;/a&gt;) into the company to manage medium to large projects using agile methods replacing the &amp;lsquo;waterfall&amp;rsquo; mentality that only suited small projects.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Handled and improved the recruitment and interviewing of software engineers from China and overseas. Supported HR with writing job descriptions for hiring open and new positions. Data analysis of the history of hired candidates to improve the efficiency and focus of our hiring efforts. Wrote C++ and C# test papers for HR to use to test candidates.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;guerrilla-games-amsterdam-nl-http-www-guerrilla-games-com:8ecf1b6ee153f5f9713e1277d3ae6be8&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://www.guerrilla-games.com/&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;GUERRILLA GAMES &amp;ndash; Amsterdam, NL&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&#34;senior-lead-programmer-2000-to-2005:8ecf1b6ee153f5f9713e1277d3ae6be8&#34;&gt;Senior/Lead Programmer, 2000 to 2005&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Led project programming tasks including enhancements, maintenance and support for products and tools. Engineered software systems, handling detailed analysis and intricate programming to meet project requirements.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Accomplishments:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Led engineering efforts that dealt with process automation, data conversion and functionality enhancements. Replaced, error-prone manual processes with elegant, automated solutions.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Developed and implemented supportive tools that are configurable and extensible to support their data conversion framework.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Developed and implemented an advanced particle simulation system with an objective of reusing memory to avoid frequent memory allocations and reducing memory footprint.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;ict-group-rotterdam-nl-http-ict-eu-nl:8ecf1b6ee153f5f9713e1277d3ae6be8&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://ict.eu/nl/&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;ICT GROUP &amp;ndash; Rotterdam, NL&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&#34;programmer-iii-march-1998-to-december-2000:8ecf1b6ee153f5f9713e1277d3ae6be8&#34;&gt;Programmer III, March 1998 to December 2000&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Worked in a small team of 8 professional software engineers developing a public transport bus system as a combination of software and hardware. Using &lt;a href=&#34;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Unified_Modeling_Language&#34;&gt;UML&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href=&#34;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Rational_Software_Modeler&#34;&gt;Rational Rose&lt;/a&gt; to design new or modify existing system designs, followed by implementation or refactoring complemented with test suits and documentation.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Received training in communication and assertiveness, software engineering and management.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;lostboys-games-amsterdam-nl-https-en-wikipedia-org-wiki-lost-boys-games:8ecf1b6ee153f5f9713e1277d3ae6be8&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Lost_Boys_Games&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;LOSTBOYS GAMES &amp;ndash; Amsterdam, NL&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&#34;media-software-programmer-i-programmer-ii-1996-to-1998:8ecf1b6ee153f5f9713e1277d3ae6be8&#34;&gt;Media Software Programmer I / Programmer II, 1996 to 1998&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Progressed through promotions, culminating in responsibility for 2d and 3d-based application programming focused on multi-media. Became adept in optimizing code for performance as well as standardizing libraries for enabling system testing and debugging.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;pannekeet-machine-tech-alkmaar-nl-https-jasa-nl-nl:8ecf1b6ee153f5f9713e1277d3ae6be8&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://jasa.nl/nl&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;PANNEKEET MACHINE TECH &amp;ndash; Alkmaar, NL&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&#34;industrial-machines-company-plc-programmer-1995-to-1996:8ecf1b6ee153f5f9713e1277d3ae6be8&#34;&gt;Industrial Machines Company, PLC Programmer, 1995 to 1996&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Worked as an individual on supporting machinery with &lt;a href=&#34;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Programmable_logic_controller&#34;&gt;PLC&lt;/a&gt; software to automate machines using sensors and actuators to control their flow and operation. Introduced the use of finite state machines (&lt;a href=&#34;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Finite-state_machine&#34;&gt;FSM&lt;/a&gt;) and hierarchical &lt;a href=&#34;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Finite-state_machine&#34;&gt;FSM&lt;/a&gt; to the process of developing software where before there was no structured approach, by adding additional debugging information to state-machines as well as solid documentation on the states and their transitions ‘debugging’ was greatly improved for engineers but even for customers.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;education-credentials:8ecf1b6ee153f5f9713e1277d3ae6be8&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Education &amp;amp; Credentials&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;HTS &amp;ndash; Alkmaar, NL&lt;br /&gt;
BS in Electrical Engineering, 1990 to 1994&lt;br /&gt;
Graduated in Measurement and Control Systems&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Certifications:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;SCRUM Alliance, SCRUM Master, 2008&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Recent Seminars:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;C++11 Programming Concepts&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;C++ Programming Concepts, Design and Implementation&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Workshop in Object-Oriented Analysis and Design&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>