<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Resumes on Personal Information</title>
    <link>http://jurgen-kluft.github.io/resumes/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Resumes on Personal Information</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-EN</language>
    <managingEditor>jurgen.kluft@gmail.com (Jurgen)</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>jurgen.kluft@gmail.com (Jurgen)</webMaster>
    <copyright>Jurgen</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 11 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://jurgen-kluft.github.io/resumes/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://jurgen-kluft.github.io/resumes/motivation-en/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>jurgen.kluft@gmail.com (Jurgen)</author>
      <guid>http://jurgen-kluft.github.io/resumes/motivation-en/</guid>
      <description>Motivation Looking for challenges especially in tools and technology. Optimizing, debug tools, data processing, workflow tools, (game engine) systems, automated testing, data analysis.
Have a lot of experience with C and C++ as well as C# and Golang. In the past i have also written a lot of MC68000 assembly language and afterwards also PIC and Zilog micro controller assembly. The recent years it has been SSE/AVX and NEON for ARM.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://jurgen-kluft.github.io/resumes/motivation-nl/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>jurgen.kluft@gmail.com (Jurgen)</author>
      <guid>http://jurgen-kluft.github.io/resumes/motivation-nl/</guid>
      <description>Motivatie Ben op zoek naar uitdagingen vooral in tools en technologie. Optimalisaties, debug tools, data processing, workflow tools, (game engine) systems, automated testing, data analyses.
Heb erg veel ervarning in C/C++, maar ook in C# en Golang. Verder heb ik vroeger heel veel assembly geschreven in MC68000 met daarna hier en daar assembly voor PIC en Zilog micro controllers. De laatse jaren is het meer SSE/AVX en NEON voor ARM geworden.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://jurgen-kluft.github.io/resumes/resume-en/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>jurgen.kluft@gmail.com (Jurgen)</author>
      <guid>http://jurgen-kluft.github.io/resumes/resume-en/</guid>
      <description>Resume TECHNICAL DIRECTOR, SOFTWARE ENGINEERING I am a Senior Software Engineer working at a major game company in Shanghai (China). In the past I have worked at various other big companies in the Netherlands including Guerrilla Games (Amsterdam) and ICT (Rotterdam). I am passionate about Technology. Apart from C++/C# I have special interest in high performance and embedded systems as well as P2P technologies.
PERSONAL INFO Gender: Male
Date of Birth: June 19, 1971</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>